we're going to cover the support for
我们将涵盖对
unit 5 in IntelliJ IDEA 2016 point 2
IntelliJ IDEA 2016第2点中的单元5
we're going to cover the changes to the
我们将介绍对
debugger will cover the changes to
调试器将涵盖对
version control will cover inspections
版本控制将涵盖检查
the editor couple of editor changes some
编辑器的几个编辑器更改了一些
small UI changes and then we'll cover
小小的UI更改，然后我们将介绍
changes to database tools and the
更改数据库工具和
JavaScript changes that have gone into
已进行的JavaScript变更
IntelliJ IDEA there's the one thing we
IntelliJ IDEA我们有一件事
won't be covering which usually falls
通常不会掉下来
under an intelligence West Java webinar
在西JAVA智能网络研讨会下
is the spring changes because as a
是春天的变化，因为
webinar specifically to cover that so we
网络研讨会专门涵盖了这一点，所以我们
won't cover that in this one so moving
不会在这一篇中涵盖
straight ahead the first thing I'd like
我想做的第一件事
to cover is the support for J unit 5 I
涵盖的是对J单元5 I的支持
haven't talked about this in one of the
还没有在其中一个谈论过
screencasts yet and we haven't covered
截屏，我们还没有介绍
it in any depth in a blog post yet so
它在博客文章中的任何深度都没有
this is this is quite new information
这是相当新的信息
that I'm going to be sharing with you
我要和你分享
guys
伙计们
so IntelliJ IDEA 2016 point two does
所以IntelliJ IDEA 2016第二点
come with support for the brand shiny
附带对闪亮品牌的支持
new J unit 5 now most of us as Java
新的J单元5现在我们大多数人都使用Java
developers should have been using J unit
开发人员应该一直在使用J单元
probably for many many years and the new
大概很多年了，新的
version is going is quite eagerly
版本即将推出
awaited and could involve quite a few
等待，可能涉及很多
changes to the way that we the way that
改变我们的方式
we run tests the way that we think about
我们以思考的方式进行测试
tests so it's quite nice to see that
测试，所以很高兴看到
IntelliJ supports it already even though
尽管IntelliJ已经支持它
it's still in state of development so
它仍处于发展状态
let me show you what some of that looks
让我告诉你一些看起来
like so this is an example J unit 5 test
像这样，这是一个J单元5测试示例
this is a kind of fairly simple
这是一种相当简单的
straightforward example where we have
我们拥有的简单示例
test manager
测试经理
patient but this is the new test
病人，但这是新的测试
annotation not the not the old one and
注释不是不是旧的和
I'm using the display name annotation as
我正在使用显示名称注释
well I'll show I'll run these tests so
好吧，我将展示我将运行这些测试，以便
you can see a that it works and B what
您可以看到a可以正常运行，B可以
that looks like
看起来像
so you can see that when we run this
所以你可以看到当我们运行这个
j-unit Jupiter is the the new J unit
j单位Jupiter是新的J单位
five runner and you can see that it
五名亚军，你可以看到
actually outputs the display name of the
实际输出的显示名称
test rather than the test method name so
测试而不是测试方法名称
you should be able to see in the results
您应该能够在结果中看到
of the test when you run them you should
测试时，您应该
be able to see a useful description of
能够看到关于
the test that ran whether it passed or
是否通过了测试
failed another thing which is new in J
失败了J中的另一件事
unit 5 is this ability to assert all and
单元5是断言所有和
a run number of assertions in a single
单个中的多个断言
block and that's supported in in
块，并且在中受支持
IntelliJ IDEA as well another example of
IntelliJ IDEA以及
this
这个
let's have a look at this one J unit 5
让我们来看看这个J单元5
allows you to nest these test cases so
允许您嵌套这些测试用例，以便
what I've done here is I've nested them
我在这里所做的就是将它们嵌套
as a kind of in a given one and then
作为一种给定的，然后
style way these inner classes are a
这些内部类的样式方式是
specific set of specifications so in
一组特定的规范
this case any happy messages as opposed
这种情况下，任何与之相反的快乐信息
to any sad messages and then inside
到任何悲伤的讯息，然后在里面
those we've got nested tests as well so
那些我们也有嵌套测试的
I'll show you what this looks like when
我会告诉你这是什么样子
it runs and you can see the nested
它运行，您可以看到嵌套
specifications here so you see the when
规格在这里，所以你看到什么时候
and then you see a series of shoulds so
然后你会看到一系列的应该
this is all fully supported in IntelliJ
IntelliJ完全支持这一切
IDEA 2016 point two J unit five is
IDEA 2016点二J单元五是
currently under development as is the
目前正在开发中
support for J unit five so you'll see
支持J单元五，您将看到
some of these things you'll see them
其中一些东西，你会看到它们
changing and improving as these things
改变和改善这些事情
go on but for now just be aware the fact
继续，但是现在只知道事实
that if you do want to start playing
如果你想开始玩
with J unit five it is supported fully
使用J单元5完全支持
inside the IDE so that's that yes there
在IDE中，所以在那里
are the new annotations that support it
是支持它的新注释
from Dana five and the display of the
从达纳五世和展示
results next thing I want to cover while
结果我想涵盖的下一件事
we sort of on the testing area is I want
我们想要在测试区域上进行排序
to cover the changes and improvements to
涵盖对
the debugger we have merged the watches
我们合并了手表的调试器
in variables windows and we've added
在变量窗口中，我们添加了
multi-line expression support in a bunch
一堆多行表达支持
of different places so let's take a
不同的地方，让我们来
quick look at those things so firstly
首先快速看一下这些东西
let me find
让我找到
to run if I debug this
如果我调试它运行
now inside the variables window you can
现在在变量窗口中，您可以
add a watch expression if you want if
如果需要，添加监视表达式
you want a separate window for your
您想要一个单独的窗口
watches you can still bring that up and
手表，你仍然可以提出来，
have that in a separate window if you
如果您将其放在单独的窗口中
like or you can merge them all into a
喜欢，也可以将它们全部合并为一个
single place so let's say for example
一个地方，所以让我们举个例子
here we might want to add a new watch
在这里我们可能要添加新手表
for example and then you can see all of
例如，然后您可以看到所有
your watches in the same window as all
您的手表与所有手表都在同一个窗口中
of the variables as they change this is
变量的变化，这是
quite useful this means that we don't
非常有用，这意味着我们不会
have to have a number of different
必须有许多不同的
places to look at what the state of
看一下状态的地方
various things are but as I said that
各种各样的事情，但是正如我所说的
you can still have the separate things
你仍然可以拥有分开的东西
if you want to the other main change
如果您要其他主要更改
here is the support for multi-line
这是对多行的支持
expressions so if we look if we right
表达式，所以如果我们看是否正确
click on this breakpoint we can add a
点击这个断点，我们可以添加一个
condition condition so that this
条件条件这样
breakpoint will only stop under certain
断点只会在特定情况下停止
circumstances the now supports
现在支持的情况
multi-line expressions so here let's say
多行表达式，所以这里说
we want to support we want to stop at
我们想要支持我们想停下来
this breakpoint when this particular
这个断点的时候特别
condition is met this allows you to
满足条件，这使您能够
build up a more complex expression to
建立更复杂的表达
evaluate to decide whether or not you
评估以确定您是否
want to stop at this breakpoint and by
想在此断点处停下来
having this multi-line expression if we
如果我们有这个多行表达式
enable that then we should see its ill
使那我们应该看到它的病
stops there under those circumstances
在那种情况下停在那里
the other places where this has been
在其他地方
added are if we go over here we can also
添加的是，如果我们经过这里，我们还可以
in evaluate a log we can add a
在评估日志中，我们可以添加一个
multi-line expression as well so here
多行表达式也是如此
maybe I want to log what that length of
也许我想记录一下
that array was I can I can put that here
该阵列是我可以把它放在这里
that's enabled and then when I run this
启用，然后当我运行此
let me get to there as
让我到达那里
you'll see the you'll see that
你会看到你会看到
expression logs here and the final place
表达式记录在这里和最后的地方
which supports multi-line expressions
支持多行表达式
and is in the custom datatype renders so
并且在自定义数据类型中呈现为
bring that up using actions
使用动作提出来
nowadays up renderers are allow or wait
如今，渲染器允许或等待
for you to tell the IDE what information
让您告诉IDE什么信息
you want to show about a particular type
您想要显示特定类型
when for example you're debugging so if
例如，当您在调试时，如果
I want to have a look at what this
我想看看这是什么
Twitter connection thing is what what
Twitter的连接东西是什么
expression do I use to decide on how to
我用来决定如何表达
display that so here again we have this
显示，所以在这里我们再次有这个
multi-line expression I'm going to use a
多行表达式，我将使用
spring a string builder to build up a
弹起弦构建器以建立一个
descriptive string for this particular
此特定的描述性字符串
object it might be that I don't want to
反对可能是我不想
it might be that I don't want to
可能是我不想
override to string to provide a pretty
覆盖字符串以提供一个漂亮的
string for this object I might want to
我可能想要此对象的字符串
provide a custom string for the IDE to
为IDE提供自定义字符串以
display this so here I've added this
显示这个，所以我在这里添加了这个
here and let me show you how that works
在这里，让我向您展示它的工作原理
so if I enable that I'll go to somewhere
所以如果我启用我会去某个地方
which is using that so that was this
使用的是那个
Twitter connection object and when I
Twitter连接对象以及当我
debug this you can see let's remove that
调试一下，您可以看到让我们删除它
watch because I don't need it anymore
看，因为我不再需要它了
you can see this Twitter connection is
您可以看到此Twitter连接是
using my custom expression to display
使用我的自定义表达式来显示
the information about it okay so that's
关于它的信息还可以，所以
the the two main features of the changes
变化的两个主要特征
that have happened to the debugger the
调试器发生了什么
watch isn't variables being merged and
注意变量是否不被合并
multi-line expression support being
多行表达支持
extended to number of different places
扩展到不同地方的数量
and are there any questions at this
对此有任何疑问
point
点
yeah we have a couple of questions and
是的，我们有几个问题，
the first one is about some very
第一个是关于一些非常
specific problem regarding spring MVC
关于Spring MVC的特定问题
support so at the moment I believe it's
支持，所以目前我相信这是
better to be reported to our tracker
最好向我们的追踪器报告
because I can't say for sure why it
因为我不能确定为什么
happens without taking a look at to the
发生而不看
actual code so yeah I would suggest to
实际的代码，所以我建议
go to the tracker and check if there is
去追踪器，检查是否有
already existing issue about that were
已经存在的问题是
just reported and the dog has to get it
刚刚报告，狗必须得到它
fixed so now that question is about
修复，所以现在这个问题是关于
Kotlin on any new features in 2016 point
Kotlin关于2016年点的任何新功能
two
二
for costly not much but there are if you
成本不高，但如果您有
a couple of features actually going to
实际上要使用的几个功能
will make it to the nearest update so in
将其更新为最近的
you know he be built in for 2016 point
你知道他会在2016年建立
two point one you already can try the
两点一，你已经可以尝试
new cuddling plug-in version updated to
新的拥抱插件版本已更新为
one point zero point three so the new
一分零分三分所以新
features are a little bit smart code
功能有点聪明的代码
completion so now it respects some very
完成，所以现在它尊重一些
specific statements like by and in and
具体陈述，例如by和in和
suggest smart completion they are all
建议聪明的完成他们都是
they're also available the new action
他们也可以使用新动作
move elements right and left previously
先前左右移动元素
added for Java so now it will work for
为Java添加的，因此现在可以使用
cotton and cotton byte code to window
棉花和棉花字节码到窗口
also get a decompile button so you can
还可以得到一个反编译按钮
decompile your byte code and see the
反编译您的字节码并查看
cotton source code and I believe
棉花源代码，我相信
there'll be more so stay tuned and the
还有更多，敬请期待，
second question is about inspections and
第二个问题是关于检查和
the problems pain so the question is
问题很痛苦，所以问题是
yeah should we cover that when we once
是的，当我们一次
we've gone over the inspections changes
我们已经完成了检查变更
I think I can answer it now because it
我想我现在可以回答，因为它
doesn't relate to their new features so
与他们的新功能无关
it basically asks if we could in
它基本上问我们是否可以
IntelliJ IDEA show problems related to
IntelliJ IDEA显示与以下问题有关
not only Oh currently open file but but
哦，不仅当前打开文件，而且
old files in the project for example
例如项目中的旧文件
like it leaves does and we do have such
就像叶子一样，我们确实有
plans and we considering such option it
计划，我们考虑这样的选择
it's not ready yet so I really hope to
还没有准备好，所以我真的希望
see it myself
自己看
so far you could enable the automatic
到目前为止，您可以启用自动
compilation your compiler setting and
编译您的编译器设置，然后
you'll see the the problems tool window
您会看到问题工具窗口
and it may probably be what you actually
可能就是你真正的
need but still we have we have plans for
需要，但我们仍有计划
adding better support for that so but it
为此增加了更好的支持，但是它
is just not ready yet
还没准备好
and another question is about when the
另一个问题是关于何时
spring related webinar
春季相关网络研讨会
gonna be so I think I'll just send a
将会如此，我想我会发送一个
link it's gonna be in in in a few days
链接它将在几天内
yeah yeah and another question is
是的，另一个问题是
whether the debugger improvements
调试器是否有所改进
eventually make their way into pycharm
最终进入pycharm
also yeah for sure so pycharm is about
也可以肯定，所以pycharm是关于
to be released right very soon and it'll
即将发布，它将
get all their plate from improvements
从改进中获得全部收益
from IntelliJ IDEA and I think that's it
来自IntelliJ IDEA，我想就是这样
for now okay great
现在好极了
so I'll move on to the next thing which
所以我继续下一个
is the changes to version control so
是版本控制的更改，因此
they've been some small improvements to
他们对
version control well I shouldn't I
版本控制很好，我不应该
shouldn't say small improvements I don't
不应该说我没有小的改进
know how much effort it took to
知道花了多少精力
implement them but in terms of from the
实施它们，但从
users point of view there are some nice
用户的观点有一些不错的
there are some nice changes to version
版本有一些不错的变化
control which are not a massive impact
控制不是很大的影响
which has changed the way you work a
这改变了你的工作方式
little bit firstly what I think is
首先，我认为是
probably addressed to some of my
可能是针对我的一些人
frustrations let me just open the right
挫折让我只是打开正确的门
project for this
为此项目
the the log window has a number of
日志窗口中有许多
improvements so in the version control
改进，以便在版本控制中
log the the performance of this window
记录此窗口的性能
is just much much better than it used to
比以前好多了
be the the changes get loaded in the
是将更改加载到
background and so rather than in the
背景等等，而不是在
past something I noticed is that when
我注意到的过去是
you come to this window it takes a
你来到这个窗口需要一个
little while to load now I find that the
加载一会儿，我发现
loading is much much quicker there's
加载要快得多
also an updated progress bar which
还有更新的进度条
appears underneath these buttons here
出现在这些按钮的下方
when it's loading some changes but I've
当它加载一些更改，但我已经
only seen that about twice since the new
自新版以来只看到过两次
update because the changes get loaded so
更新，因为更改已加载，因此
quickly that the performance of this
很快，这个的表现
screen is much much better another
屏幕要好得多
change in here is that
这里的变化是
if we want to select more than one
如果我们要选择多个
commit so like this with a few files
像这样提交一些文件
some information and a commit here with
一些信息和在这里提交
some different files when we select both
同时选择一些不同的文件
those commits we can see the combined
这些提交，我们可以看到合并
value of those commits we can see both
这些提交的价值，我们可以看到
messages and we can see all the files
消息，我们可以看到所有文件
that changed that's quite a nice way of
改变了，这是一个很好的方法
seeing you know if you want to take a
看到你知道你是否想参加
quick look at some changes on a branch
快速查看分支上的一些更改
how much was changed in in those
这些改变了多少
individual commits and another quick
个人提交和另一个快速
change is the ability to navigate using
变化是使用导航的能力
command l and if you run wondering which
命令l，如果您想知道哪个
shortcuts I'm using that goes down at
我正在使用的快捷方式在
the bottom of the screen at command L or
屏幕底部的命令L或
control L for Windows and Linux takes
Windows和Linux的控件L需要
you into the search box so then I can
您进入搜索框，这样我就可以
type the search and find out any
键入搜索并找出任何
messages which oops under on then find
出现在下面的消息然后找到
any commits which mention Landers for
任何提及Landers的提交
example whatever that's had quite a lot
举例说明有很多东西
of improvements are around applying
的改进围绕着应用
patches so for a start there's a couple
补丁，所以一开始有几个
of different ways of applying these
应用这些的不同方式
patches firstly
首先打补丁
if we had something like if we drag our
如果我们有像我们拖曳我们的东西
patch into the idea window it will live
修补到将打开的想法窗口中
coding live demos are always it is a
编码现场演示始终是
that's it is waiting to happen
这就是等待发生的事情
it should let's try it again okay it
应该让我们再试一次
will open up the apply patch dialog just
将会打开“应用补丁”对话框
from dragging the patch into the window
从将补丁拖到窗口中
and then you can apply that patch
然后您可以应用该补丁
you can also that's the patch is a text
您也可以说补丁是文本
value you can also if you have one of
如果您具有以下一项，也可以
these things open if I select the
如果我选择
contents of this and then the folk move
内容，然后民间搬家
the focus back to the IDE I haven't had
重点回到我还没有的IDE
any press anything I don't have to do
任何我不需要做的新闻
anything it will just automatically try
任何会自动尝试的东西
and apply that patch now this is
并应用该补丁，现在是
particularly useful if someone emails
如果有人发送电子邮件，此功能特别有用
you a patch or if you see a patch file
您是补丁程序，还是看到补丁程序文件
on on a web application or something
在网络应用程序上
like that well you don't want to
就像那样，你不想
download the physical file you've just
下载您刚刚的物理文件
got it on the clipboard this is quite an
把它放在剪贴板上
effective way to apply those patches and
应用这些补丁的有效方法
one of the other things that's happened
发生的另一件事
around applying patches is that IntelliJ
关于应用补丁的是IntelliJ
has just got that much smarter about
刚刚变得更聪明
applying these patches for example here
例如在此处应用这些补丁
it tells me I have a missing base file
告诉我我缺少基本文件
because this file was renamed since the
因为此文件自
patch was created so I can select that I
补丁已创建，因此我可以选择
can select the updated file if I want to
可以选择更新的文件
it will try and do a number of things
它将尝试做很多事情
automatically for you so that you don't
自动为您服务，这样您就不会
have to do those kinds of manual steps
必须做那些手动步骤
as well I haven't been able to reproduce
我也无法复制
every single circumstance under which
在任何情况下
these patches can be now magically
这些补丁现在可以神奇地
applied but if you do if you are in the
应用，但如果您在
process of applying patches regularly
定期应用补丁的过程
you should see some improvements in this
您应该会看到一些改进
area and one of the other changes I
区域和其他变化之一
quite like is let's open up
就像是让我们打开
this file here if I create a new file
如果我创建一个新文件，请在此文件
let's call it the file and if I forget
我们称它为文件，如果我忘记了
to add it to get or decide at the
添加它以获取或决定
beginning I'm not going to add it to get
开始我不会添加它来得到
when I actually go and try and commit
当我真正去尝试并承诺
any changes I can
我可以做的任何改变
now see in here all my own version files
现在在这里看到我所有的版本文件
so if I forgot to commit this file if I
所以如果我忘记提交这个文件
forgot to add it to get or if it came
忘记添加它来获取它，或者它来了
from another system perhaps I perhaps
从另一个系统也许我也许
this file was added not through IntelliJ
此文件不是通过IntelliJ添加的
it will allow you to select these new
它将允许您选择这些新
files so you don't accidentally forget
文件，这样您就不会意外忘记
to commit may be generated files and so
提交可能是生成的文件等等
on and so forth so let's commit that and
依此类推，让我们提交
another change is that case only renames
另一个变化是只重命名
have they work the way that you expect
他们以您期望的方式工作
them to work on both the Mac and on
它们可以在Mac和Mac上使用
Windows so I'm using a Mac here so let's
Windows，所以我在这里使用Mac，所以让我们
say I rename this file but I call it the
说我重命名了这个文件，但是我称它为
file just with a different case when I
我只是用不同的情况归档
refer to that so let's see that that's
提到那个，让我们看看那是
got the new name this gets committed
有了新名称，就可以提交了
correctly if we go back to the log we
正确地，如果我们回到日志，
can see we have the two files for the
可以看到我们有两个文件
different cases and then let's say I
不同的情况，然后说我
roll back to this commit here
在此处回滚到此提交
the correct case so those are the sort
正确的情况，所以这些都是
of main highlighted changes of that have
主要突出变化的
happened to version control in IntelliJ
发生在IntelliJ中的版本控制
IDEA 2016 point 2 next up let's cover
IDEA 2016要点2接下来让我们介绍一下
some of the inspection changes so mainly
一些检查变更主要是
the tool window around inspections has
检查周围的工具窗口有
been redesigned and you'll notice this
经过重新设计，您会注意到这一点
as soon as you run the first the first
只要您先运行第一个
set of inspections if I look
我看一套检查
results here so I've already been
结果在这里，所以我已经
through the process of saying analyze
通过说分析的过程
inspect code and picking a profile to
检查代码并选择一个配置文件
inspect and these are my results here
检查，这是我的结果
this is fairly familiar but now when you
这是相当熟悉的，但是现在当你
click on one of these things you'll see
单击您将看到的其中一项
here the the code the whole code area
这里的代码是整个代码区
around that inspection violation and so
围绕检查违规等等
this allows me to do a number of
这使我可以做一些
different things I can either apply the
我可以应用不同的东西
suggested change here I can suppress
建议的更改在这里我可以抑制
this inspection for the statement of the
此检查的陈述
method of the class I can go in here and
该类的方法，我可以进入这里
manipulate the code if I want to so I
如果我愿意，可以操纵代码
can do replace at lambda here or if I
可以在这里的lambda上进行替换，或者如果我
want I can
希望我能
navigate directly to the code and take a
直接导航到代码，然后
look at the code in the context to the
在上下文中查看代码
whole file like I used to be able to
像我以前那样的整个文件
this is just quite a nice quick way to
这只是一个不错的快速方法
be able to go through your inspection
能够通过您的检查
results and apply the changes if you
结果并应用更改（如果您
want to i found this particularly useful
想要我发现这特别有用
when i'm trying to migrate some of my
当我尝试迁移一些我的
code to to job 8 for example i'm using
代码以作业8例如我正在使用
the java language java language level
Java语言Java语言级别
migration aids quite a lot to see which
迁移帮助很多，看看哪个
one of these inspections i can apply
我可以申请这些检查之一
there's also a new inspection it's
还有一个新的检查
usually new inspections in most new
通常在大多数新产品中进行新检查
versions of the ide they tend to pop up
他们倾向于弹出的ide版本
and you don't want doesn't really keep
而你不想要并没有真正保持
up to date and notice them so let's have
最新，并注意到他们，所以让我们有
a look at this new inspection here i can
看看这里的新检查
actually apply a filter to find out
实际应用过滤器来找出
which new inspections have appeared in
出现了哪些新检查
the latest version I'm running the 2016
我正在运行2016的最新版本
point-to-point one
点对点一
EAP and so that's the version that I've
EAP，这就是我的版本
got here but let's say I want to have a
到了这里，但假设我要一个
look at the new inspections in 2016
看一下2016年的新检查
point two this is a new inspection which
第二点，这是一项新的检查
lets you know if you're creating new
告诉您是否要创建新的
objects inside methods like equals hash
像equals hash这样的方法中的对象
code compared to and because these
代码相比，因为
methods are used regularly particularly
特别是定期使用方法
inside collections and so forth so if
内部收藏等等，如果
you are creating a brand new object
您正在创建一个全新的对象
inside the equals method for example you
在equals方法中，例如您
might be incurring a significant penalty
可能会受到重大处罚
hit so by enabling this very enabling
通过启用此非常启用来实现
this inspection and running that
这次检查并运行
inspection you might find some places
检查您可能会发现一些地方
where you can get some performance quick
您可以在其中快速获得一些性能
wins so there's the kind of main
赢了，所以有一种主要的
areas for inspections I was just taking
我刚带的检查区域
a look to see if there are any more
看看是否还有更多
questions
问题
I think I'll pause for questions after
我想我会停下来提问
the next section okay so next up some
下一节好吧，接下来一些
changes around the editor we have some
编辑器周围的变化，我们有一些
noticeable changes like breadcrumbs for
明显的变化，例如面包屑
Java we have support for ligatures and
Java我们支持连字和
we have some more support for writing
我们还有更多的写作支持
regular expressions you might have
您可能拥有的正则表达式
noticed I enabled breadcrumbs up here in
注意到我在这里启用了面包屑
the top and the top bar here you can see
您可以在此处看到顶部和顶部栏
wherever I am wherever my cursor is it
无论我在哪里，无论光标在哪里
tells me which class I'm in and which
告诉我我在哪堂课上
method I'm in and this may seem a fairly
我正在使用的方法，这似乎是一个相当
simple in a case like this where I'm
在我这样的情况下很简单
just in a in a method inside a class but
只是在类中的方法中
once we start getting into nested
一旦我们开始进入嵌套
classes let's have a look at those tests
让我们来看看那些测试
we were looking at early on for a start
我们很早就开始寻找
when we're inside a let's minimize the
当我们在里面时，让我们最小化
buttons when were inside a lambda
在lambda内时的按钮
expression then we can see which method
表达式，然后我们可以看到哪种方法
were in and the fact that we're in a
的事实，我们在
lambda we can if we go to that nested
lambda我们可以，如果我们去嵌套
class where we have a top-level class
我们有一个顶级班级的班级
and inner class and a method then our
还有内部类和方法，然后我们
breadcrumbs tell us exactly where we are
面包屑告诉我们确切的位置
in each of these cases so this is
在每种情况下，这是
something you might want to choose to
您可能想要选择的东西
turn on particularly with complex code
用复杂的代码打开
or code that extensively uses things
或广泛使用事物的代码
like lambda expressions or you can turn
例如lambda表达式，或者您可以打开
it off by I'm using find action to tie
我正在使用查找动作来绑定它
it off but actually you can just go into
它关闭，但实际上您可以进入
settings editor general appearance and
设置编辑器的一般外观和
turn off show breadcrumbs so that way
关闭显示面包屑，这样
you
您
toggle it on or off and another nice
打开或关闭它，另一个不错
change that's happened is if we go to
发生的改变是如果我们去
somewhere that uses lambda expressions
使用lambda表达式的地方
Java code here we've got a couple of
这里的Java代码有几个
lambda expressions inside the stream in
流中的lambda表达式
my settings I can enable I can enable
我可以启用的设置我可以启用
font ligatures I have to select a font
字体连字我必须选择一种字体
that supports font ligatures like for
支持像这样的字体连字
example this one or this one so I have
例如这个或这个，所以我有
to know which of my fonts supports
知道我的字体支持
literatures but if I pick one of these
文学，但如果我选择其中之一
and then enable it what you'll see is is
然后启用它，您将看到的是
your lambda expressions get turned into
你的lambda表达式变成
proper arrows things like not equals get
正确的箭头之类的东西不等于得到
turned into the mathematical symbol and
变成了数学符号，
so forth and and this is just a
等等，这只是一个
rendering thing so we should be able to
渲染东西，所以我们应该能够
say hey if I type mood not equal then
说嘿，如果我输入的心情不相等，那么
you can see it just gets converted
你可以看到它刚刚被转换
straight to the the new representation
直接使用新的表示形式
under the covers it's exactly the same
在被窝里完全一样
thing it's just being rendered in a
它只是在一个
slightly different way this might be
可能略有不同
something that you prefer to use if
您喜欢使用的东西
you're using a more functional style of
您使用的是更实用的样式
programming or if it's just something
编程或仅仅是什么
that makes you feel more comfortable I'm
让你更舒服我
going to defend that off for now so I
现在要为它辩护，所以我
can remember which ones I was on in fact
记得我实际上在哪一个
you can see if I've got this enabled but
您可以查看是否已启用此功能，但是
I'm using the default font then you
我使用的是默认字体，然后
won't see you won't see the arrows and
不会看到你不会看到箭头和
the pretty equals or not equal signs and
漂亮的等号或不等号
the
的
all change in the final new thing in the
最终的新事物中的所有变化
editors is more improvements to helping
编辑者在帮助方面还有更多改进
you write regular expressions so I'm not
你写正则表达式，所以我不是
sure about you guys but I always have to
确定你们，但我总是必须
look up how to use regular expressions
查找如何使用正则表达式
and IntelliJ IDEA has a bunch of things
IntelliJ IDEA有很多东西
to help us do this so let me give you an
帮助我们做到这一点，所以让我给你一个
example regular expression there I've
我有示例正则表达式
just used them a cheat so that I didn't
只是用他们作弊，所以我没有
have to type it out manually to make
必须手动将其键入
sure I got it right and so let's say
确定我做对了，所以我们说
we've got a regular expression like this
我们有一个这样的正则表达式
now we get Auto we get code completion
现在我们得到自动我们得到代码完成
for the groups that are put in the
对于放在
regular expression so I can get Auto
正则表达式，这样我就可以自动
completion code completion on the group
组上的完成代码完成
name and if I use that and I've done
名称，如果我使用它，我已经完成了
something wrong as I have done in this
我做错了
case then I'm getting some I'm getting
情况下，我得到一些我得到
errors reported to me to tell me what
错误报告给我，告诉我什么
I've done wrong with this regular
我这个常规做错了
expression I can also of course I can
表达我当然也可以
also check my regular expression and put
还检查我的正则表达式，并把
in some example code to some example
在某些示例代码中
text to see whether I can get a match or
文字以查看我是否可以找到比赛或
not let's roll that back because I put
不要因为我放回去
an error in there on purpose okay so
故意有一个错误，所以
next up is there are some small changes
接下来有一些小变化
to the UI that you might notice there's
到用户界面，您可能会注意到
been some changes to notifications and
对通知进行了一​​些更改，
the ability to add a background image
添加背景图像的能力
notifications I was sort of expecting
我有点期待的通知
there a notification might pop up at
那里可能会弹出通知
some point during me using the UI but it
在使用UI的过程中有一点，但它
hasn't so far but you'll find that
到目前为止还没有，但是您会发现
notifications are now popping up in the
通知现在在
bottom right-hand corner in a little
右下角稍微
balloon instead of in the top right
气球，而不是右上角
corner and you can configure what gets
角落，您可以配置得到
what gets popped up and what is just a
弹出的是什么
silent a silent
无声无声
either piece of information or error and
信息或错误
you might see one of these things pop up
您可能会看到其中之一弹出
as as I go throughout this usually it's
正如我在整个过程中通常
it's errors especially on there on some
这是错误，尤其是在某些地方
of the more unstable bits and pieces and
更不稳定的点点滴滴
but what is quite interesting is the
但有趣的是
ability to add a background image here I
我可以在这里添加背景图片的能力
might want to use I've use the one thing
可能想用我用过的一件事
I'm going to do
我打算去做
find action to look for a background
寻找行动寻找背景
image and I can now navigate to a
图片，现在我可以导航到
background image and let's pick
背景图片，让我们来选择
something so if I want to cuss
所以如果我想骂
that my UI looks then I can add
我的用户界面看起来就可以添加
background image and I can do things
背景图片，我可以做
like tweak the twig how opaque it is to
像调整树枝一样，它变得不透明
see just how readable the code is with
看看代码的可读性
that image on underneath it and the
该图像在其下方以及
other way that you can do this so I got
其他方式，你可以做到这一点，我得到了
here by using fine to action to navigate
通过精细操作来导航
to background image if you have an image
到背景图片（如果有图片）
for example or an image here I can also
例如，在这里我也可以
right-click this and I can set it as
右键单击它，我可以将其设置为
background image if I want to so it's
背景图片，如果我想要的话
just a nice way to to tweak the way that
只是一种调整方式的好方法
you are your UI looks just for your own
你是你的用户界面只是为了你自己
personalized Asian so that's kind of the
个性化的亚洲人，所以有点
set of basic across-the-board changes
一组基本的全面变更
you probably as mentioned you'll see
您可能如前所述会看到
some of these changes popping up in the
其中一些更改会在
other ideas like pycharm and so on and
pycharm等其他想法，以及
so forth are there any more questions at
等等还有其他问题吗
this point so far we have just one
到目前为止，我们只有一个
question about version control support
有关版本控制支持的问题
the question is about whether the new
问题是关于新
VCS features only for git or is VN as
VCS功能仅适用于git或VN为
well basically the log improvements
基本上，日志改进
available only forget and I believe all
只能忘记，我相信所有
the rest all the rest should work for
其余所有其余的应该工作
Arian as well yeah and of course use
阿里安也是，当然也要用
case only renames also work only forget
仅重命名的情况下也只能忘记
yeah thanks for that
是的，谢谢你
so the next two main areas oh yes the
所以接下来的两个主要领域
spring I mentioned that brain there is a
春天我提到大脑有一个
webinar to cover the spring specific
春季专题网络研讨会
features there's basically so much
基本上有很多功能
spring stuff in there that it deserves
春天的东西在那里值得
its own webinar that is on this Monday
它在本周一举行的网络研讨会
that's coming Monday
那是星期一
so I'm not going to cover any of those
所以我不会涵盖任何这些
features in this in this webinar but
在此网络研讨会中的功能
what I am going to cover next there are
接下来我要讲的是
two main areas that I need to cover now
我现在需要涵盖的两个主要领域
one is the changes to integrating with
一是与之整合的变化
the database and the second is around a
数据库，第二个是围绕
lot of the JavaScript improvements so
JavaScript的很多改进，所以
let's move straight on and look it's on
让我们继续前进，看看它在
the changes today it's based tools and
当今基于工具的变化以及
here's where you can see quite a number
在这里你可以看到很多
of new features have been implement
新功能的实施
so I won't read through all of these
所以我不会读所有这些
right now I will step through them and
现在，我将逐步通过它们，
demo them as we go so let me find me let
在我们进行演示时演示一下，让我找到我吧
me find a project with the database
我用数据库找到一个项目
integration so firstly one of the things
整合首先是其中之一
that's been added is code completion
添加的是代码完成
auto completion around database names
自动完成数据库名称
when we add a data source so let me add
当我们添加数据源时，让我添加
a new data source here oh sorry here I
这里有新的数据源，哦，抱歉，我
can see
可以看到
I get a list of all the databases which
我得到所有数据库的列表
I can use for this database connection I
我可以使用此数据库连接
can test that that's just a kind of
可以测试那只是一种
useful thing to make sure we don't get
确保我们不会得到帮助的有用的东西
any any missed typing errors around
任何遗漏的输入错误
database in the names in fact this
实际上名称中的数据库
version of IntelliJ has quite a few nice
IntelliJ版本有很多不错的功能
improvements to the way that auto the
自动方式的改进
way the code completion works in a
代码完成工作的方式
number of different areas particularly
特别是不同地区的数量
around databases so it gives you a lot
围绕数据库，所以它给您很多
more help next up is so something that
接下来会有更多帮助
will be familiar to us from the openness
开放会令我们熟悉
back up again so in projects when we're
再次备份，以便在项目中
looking at code and so on and so forth
看代码等等
you may have the option to auto scroll
您可以选择自动滚动
to source auto scroll from source
从源自动滚动
something that we we might use on a day
我们可能会在一天中使用的东西
to day basis and that's now available
每天，现在可用
for us in the databases window so I can
在数据库窗口中为我们服务
use auto scroll from editor if I enable
如果启用，请使用编辑器中的自动滚动
that then when I say it's something in
那当我说这是
the editor then the correct table or
编辑器，然后是正确的表或
routine or whatever will be highlighted
例行或将突出显示的内容
on the right-hand side here or if I
在这里的右侧，或者如果我
decide
决定
turn it off I can always do that by I
关掉它我总是可以做到的
can always do that manually by pressing
始终可以通过按手动进行操作
the scroll from editor button in the top
从顶部的编辑器按钮滚动
right hand corner here so I was talking
右上角所以我在说
a bit about code completion let let's
关于代码完成的一点让我们
open up one of my consoles now if I'm if
如果我现在打开我的一个控制台
I'm typing out a sequel statement when
我在输入续集声明时
it's expecting a table name then the
它期待一个表名，然后
auto completion will only suggests
自动完成只会提示
perhaps two on them so I can have
也许两个在他们身上，所以我可以
animals that species or plants or
种或植物或
species it won't suggest things like the
物种不会暗示像
routines or anything else which is not
例行程序或其他非
appropriate for this place so it still
适合这个地方，所以它仍然
that just makes the auto clear code
只是使自动清除代码
completion just a little bit more
完成多一点
helpful and a little bit less noisy and
有用的，少一点噪音，
something else is that we now have
还有一点是，我们现在有
surround with function let me show you
功能环绕让我展示给你
an example so let's just set this up so
一个例子，让我们将其设置为
we've got a reasonable example so let's
我们有一个合理的例子，让我们
say we have
说我们有
thing like this with a number of
这样的事情有很多
different a number of different columns
不同的许多不同的列
we want to select if I have something
我们想选择我是否有东西
like I can even have multi cursor here I
就像我甚至可以在这里使用多光标
can apply surround with function and as
可以将环绕声与功能配合使用
well as that if I type in the sort of
以及如果我键入
camel case if you like there the acronym
骆驼的情况下，如果你喜欢那里的首字母缩写
version of a routine name it will
例程名称的版本
suggest that so I can type in PDS and I
建议，这样我就可以输入PDS
get pretty display string there so I can
得到漂亮的显示字符串，所以我可以
select that and and that gets applied to
选择它，然后将其应用于
both of those things so that just again
这两件事，所以再次
it's just another thing which helps us
这只是另一件事，可以帮助我们
which helps us to write these things
帮助我们写这些东西
without having to do quite as much code
不必做太多的代码
up quite as much typing as in the past
与过去一样多的打字
another area where we get some
我们得到一些的另一个领域
completion which should help us is in
完成应该对我们有帮助
the values of tables so if we add a row
表的值，所以如果我们添加一行
here that says is not six when I start
我开始时说不是六个
typing B I can get some completion here
键入BI可以在这里完成一些工作
so it will offer me the options that
所以它将为我提供
begin with B that were already there if
从已经存在的B开始，如果
I want to use those or I can or I can
我想使用那些或者我可以或者我可以
select a new one if I want to and
如果我想选择一个新的
thing which is quite useful is we don't
有用的是我们不
have to use the mouse as much which is
必须尽可能多地使用鼠标
always know it always a goal of IntelliJ
永远知道这永远是IntelliJ的目标
IDEA is the ability to use keyboard
IDEA是使用键盘的能力
shortcuts work possible and so now we
快捷方式可以工作，所以现在我们
can resize columns using command shift
可以使用命令移位来调整列的大小
and arrows or shift ctrl and arrows for
和箭头或Shift Ctrl和箭头
Windows and Linux finally around the
Windows和Linux终于围绕
database integration is a number of
数据库集成是许多
different options a number of different
不同的选择很多
features to help if you're using
有助于您使用的功能
Postgres as your database so firstly the
Postgres作为您的数据库，因此首先
ability to edit range types like this
能够编辑这样的范围类型
also the ability to edit times with a
还可以使用
time zone and finally e if we open up
时区，最后是e如果我们开放
one of these consoles we can add we can
这些控制台之一，我们可以添加，我们可以
add schemas and databases to our search
在我们的搜索中添加模式和数据库
path so let's say we add this to our
路径，所以说我们将其添加到我们的
search path and then we can we can
搜索路径，然后我们可以
reorder this as well so if I move this
还要重新排序，所以如果我移动它
to the top of the search path then
然后到搜索路径的顶部
options from this table are going to
该表中的选项将转到
appear above the other options or I can
出现在其他选项上方，或者我可以
move that from there and then as I'm
从那里移动，然后当我
typing something it gives me the
输入一些东西给我
different options of plants or animals
植物或动物的不同选择
I can see there are a couple of
我可以看到有几个
questions around the database
有关数据库的问题
integration so perhaps we'll take those
集成，所以也许我们会把那些
now before we move on to anything else
现在，在我们继续前进之前
yep there are a couple of questions
是的，有几个问题
first are these database features going
首先是这些数据库功能
to be available in data group yeah they
在数据组中可用是的，他们
did a group is out and all the features
没有一个小组出去了，所有功能
shown here available there as well
显示在这里也可用
another question whether Karen
另一个问题是否凯伦
assistance available for stored
可用于存储的帮助
procedures and triggers and some for
程序和触发器，以及一些
some databases it is support already now
现在已经支持一些数据库
so you can open a stored procedure or a
因此您可以打开存储过程或
trigger for editing but for some it may
触发编辑，但对于某些触发
not be supported so it depends but I
不被支持，所以这取决于但我
expect all they did with supported a
希望他们所做的一切都支持
belief in future releases so so it
相信未来的发行版
depends if you see something not working
取决于您是否看到不起作用的东西
just report to our tracking and we'll
只需向我们的跟踪报告，我们将
get it working and one more question
使它工作，还有一个问题
about support for dynamo DB it's not
关于对dynamo DB的支持，不是
support yet and it's it's not secure
支持呢，那是不安全的
database right we do you have plans for
数据库，对，您有计划吗
supporting no single database but not
不支持单个数据库，但不支持
not in the nearest future but definitely
不在不久的将来，但是绝对
we'd like to have have it in data group
我们希望将其包含在数据组中
and IntelliJ IDEA based IDs and finally
和基于IntelliJ IDEA的ID，最后
one more question but it's not about
还有一个问题，但这不是关于
database but it is evolved greater
数据库，但它发展得更大
integration unfold the question is
整合展开的问题是
whether there any improvements regarding
关于是否有任何改进
debugging Gradle tasks i I'm afraid I
我恐怕调试Gradle任务
can't answer it now and but I'm like oh
现在无法回答，但我喜欢哦
yeah I'll try to cover it in follow-up
是的，我会尝试在后续内容中进行介绍
email so yeah sitting let's let it
电子邮件，是的，坐吧，让它
okay great let's move on to the
好吧，让我们继续前进
JavaScript changes then hey again like
JavaScript发生变化，然后又像
the database changes there's been a
数据库更改了
number of different JavaScript changes
不同的JavaScript更改次数
and of course javascript is a wide
当然javascript是广泛的
umbrella of different sorts of
不同种类的雨伞
technologies these days so I will
这些天的技术，所以我会
demonstrate some by jumping between a
通过跳一个来演示一些
number of different projects some of the
一些不同的项目
additions that we've got for for
我们需要的补充
supporting jobs but so firstly around
支持工作，但首先
air con script let's see what we've got
空调脚本让我们看看我们有什么
here
这里
so we in ekam script six IntelliJ IDEA
所以我们在ekam脚本中使用了六个IntelliJ IDEA
can suggest converting callback
可以建议转换回调
functions into arrow functions so this
功能变成箭头功能，所以这
basically for me as a mostly Java person
对我来说，基本上是Java人士
this works very similarly to the way
这与方法非常相似
that the anonymous inner classes can get
匿名内部类可以得到
converted to Landers in Java and so
在Java中转换为Landers等
there you go you just convert C to an
在那里，您只需将C转换为
error function if for example as well
错误功能，例如
you had a slightly longer form one it
你有一个稍长的形式
also offers you the option of converting
还为您提供转换的选项
these longer form ones into a shorthand
这些较长形式的速记
one okay so that's that's a new feature
好的，那就是一个新功能
that's been added in IntelliJ IDEA 2016
在IntelliJ IDEA 2016中已添加
point two and another thing that's been
第二点和另一件事
added is the postfix completion has been
添加的是后缀完成
has been built up a little bit I don't
我已经建立了一点
know if you use postfix completion it's
知道您是否使用后缀补全
something that there I've been getting
我一直在得到的东西
to grips in a little bit in the Java
在Java中掌握一点
world and but allows you to you can add
世界，但允许您添加
her you can miss type things instead of
她你可能会错过打字的东西而不是
having to go back to the beginning of a
不得不回到一个开始
line of code the idea is to allow you to
这行代码的想法是让您
continue typing in order to do things so
继续打字以便这样做
for example we supported before the
例如我们在
ability to turn something into a form
能够将某种东西变成一种形式
and by typing var and now in this
并输入var，然后在此
version oh my goodness I've got to I've
版本哦，我的天哪，我必须
got clumsy fingers going all over the
手指笨拙地遍布
place and in this version I can also
放置在这个版本中，我还可以
turn this into a Const if I want to
如果我想把它变成一个const
let's call its version or I can also
我们称其版本，或者我也可以
turn things into a lit if I so choose so
如果我选择的话，把东西变成一盏灯
let's call that template so this is just
我们称该模板为
the perfect postfix completion is just a
完美的后缀完成只是一个
nice way to allow you to continue the
允许您继续操作的好方法
flows
流
so having to move your cursor backwards
因此必须将光标向后移动
and forwards you can do dot something
并转发你可以做点东西
and there's some shortcuts which allow
还有一些捷径可以
you to do common features and that
您要做共同的功能，那
applies to Java and JavaScript and a
适用于Java和JavaScript，
bunch of other places and so that's for
一堆其他地方，所以这是为了
the Ekman script features let's move on
Ekman脚本功能让我们继续
to react features so here I have a
反应功能，所以在这里我有一个
comment box where I've defined my own
我定义了自己的注释框
prop types like title and author now
道具类型，例如标题和作者
when I start actually using this comment
当我开始实际使用此评论时
box IntelliJ IDEA will allow me to it
盒IntelliJ IDEA将允许我使用它
will provide with completion those title
将提供完整的标题
and author prop types so I I get some
和作者道具类型，所以我得到一些
nice safe code completion there a couple
不错的安全代码补全那里
of other changes here and the component
这里的其他更改和组件
lifecycle methods
生命周期方法
things like Component did mount and a
像Component这样的东西确实挂载了
number of others they don't show as
未显示为的其他数量
unused anymore in previous versions of
在以前的版本中不再使用
IntelliJ these are showing as unused
IntelliJ这些显示为未使用
which was a bit misleading so now these
这有点误导，所以现在这些
gets shown as being correctly used as
显示为正确使用
part of the framework and another thing
框架的一部分和另一件事
is the react specific attribute types
是特定于反应的属性类型
are supported so some of these are
被支持，所以其中一些是
things like key and him and my personal
像钥匙和他以及我个人的东西
favorite which is dangerously set in
危险设置的收藏夹
HTML I love anything which invokes the
HTML我喜欢任何可以调用
sense of danger so these are now
危险感，所以现在
supported with part of the auto
支持部分汽车
completion inside IntelliJ IDEA if
如果在IntelliJ IDEA中完成
you're if you're working with react and
如果您正在与React和
the final area here is if I'm using an
最后一个区域是如果我正在使用
event like on click and the code
点击和代码之类的事件
completion will give me curly braces
完成将给我大括号
instead of giving me quotes so that's
而不是给我报价，所以
just quite a nice feature to allow me to
只是一个很好的功能，让我可以
not have to keep going back and delete
不必继续返回并删除
things or or change things moving on to
事物或改变事物前进
angular 2 support we've now got some new
角2支持，我们现在有了一些新
live template support for angular 2 so I
实时模板支持angular 2，所以我
could do something like say ng 2
可以做类似ng 2的操作
component and that would just give me
组件，那只会给我
all the template stuff so again as per
所有模板的东西，所以再次按照
usual just trying to minimize the amount
通常只是试图减少数量
of typing that we have to do so I can
我必须要做的打字
now just do just navigate directly from
现在只需直接从
from thing to things wherever I want to
从事物到我想去的任何地方
be another new feature is the support
另一个新功能是支持
for let inside structural directives so
为了让内部结构指令如此
if I have something like let's say I've
如果我有类似的东西，比如说我有
got div and I've got an g4 what about
有div，我有g4
unlock it and then I can put a let in
解锁，然后我可以放进去
here and that will get properly
在这里，那将得到正确的
supported inside inside IntelliJ IDEA I
在IntelliJ IDEA I内部受支持
turn all items
转所有项目
and the final thing around around
最后的事情
angular support is if I'm creating a new
角度支持是如果我要创建一个新的
project then I can use the I can use
项目，然后我可以使用我可以使用
angular CLI so I'm selecting a static
角度CLI，所以我选择一个静态
web I can use angular CLI to create a
网络，我可以使用角度CLI创建一个
new project as long as you've got the
新项目，只要您有
angular CLI set up and installed on your
角CLI设置并安装在您的
machine so once again just a few bits
机器，所以再说一次
and pieces just to make your life a
和碎片只是为了让你的生活
little bit easier around around working
在工作周围一点点容易
with some of these JavaScript frameworks
这些JavaScript框架中的一些
the the last thing here is around build
最后一件事是构建
configurations so now what I can do
配置，现在我能做什么
let's remove this one what I can do is
让我们删除这个我可以做的是
on on a run or debug configuration I can
在运行或调试配置上，我可以
now add grunt gulp or grunt or gulp
现在添加咕unt声或咕unt声或吞咽声
tasks or NPN scripts and to run before I
任务或NPN脚本并在我运行之前
launch something else so say for example
发射其他东西，例如说
I here I'm running start there might be
我在这里我开始跑步可能会有
some particular thing I want to run
我想跑一些特别的东西
before I do that every single time so I
在我每次这样做之前，我
might want to compile my CSS or I might
可能要编译我的CSS或我可能
want to run a specific task and I can do
想执行特定任务，我可以做
that for any grunt or got tasks here so
对于任何咕gr声或有任务在这里，所以
I could say let's say it's s there and
我可以说我们在那儿，
then that will run every time I every
那我每次都会
time I decide to run that particular
我决定运行那个特定的时间
build or run configuration the last
最后构建或运行配置
thing it's not JavaScript kind of falls
事情不是JavaScript之类的
into the web front-end side of things is
进入Web前端的一面是
configuration settings for HTML so now
HTML的配置设置，现在
when you're configuring HTML so in
当您配置HTML时
obviously settings preferences editor
显然是设置偏好编辑器
HTML I can decide whether my generated
HTML，我可以决定是否生成
quote marks are single double or I don't
引号是单双或不是
have any so this just should make life a
有什么所以这应该使生活成为
little bit easier when you're striving
努力时会轻松一点
for consistency in your HTML code
保持HTML代码的一致性
data that pretty much covers the main
几乎涵盖了主要数据
things I wanted to talk about now we
我现在想谈的事情
have plenty of time to cover either any
有足够的时间来解决任何一个
remaining questions around the sections
本节其余问题
we just covered just now or any general
我们刚刚涵盖了现在或任何一般
questions around IntelliJ IDEA
有关IntelliJ IDEA的问题
thanks to be sure for a nice
谢谢一定要好
presentation so far we have just one
到目前为止，我们只有一个演讲
more question
更多问题
it is about angular CLI whether it is
关于角度CLI是否
whether its UI looks the same as for
其UI是否与的UI相同
grunt and gulp then the only UI angular
咕咕gu的然后是唯一的UI角度
CLI provides is sexually project wizard
CLI提供性项目向导
and I'm not really sure I got the
我不确定我是否知道
question so if you if you could rephrase
问题，如果你能改写
it yeah try to answer that but basically
是的，尝试回答这个问题，但是基本上
angular CLI is just an option the
角度CLI只是一个选择
project visa offers and no other UI
项目签证优惠，没有其他用户界面
available in inside the ID one question
可在ID内找到一个问题
probably it's continuation of this
可能是这的延续
question about angular CLI so that for
有关角度CLI的问题，以便
instance I click a button to link their
例如，我单击一个按钮以链接其
project sorry yeah still still still not
项目对不起是的，仍然还是没有
not not fully understand it just but not
没有完全理解它，但不是
no no worries just send it to post it to
不，不用担心，只需将其发送到
Twitter or Senate post it as a comment
Twitter或参议院发表评论
to their blog posts where will publish
到他们将在何处发布的博客文章
their economy will try to answer that
他们的经济将尽力回答
sure or ask any questions to me and
确定或问任何问题给我，
Trisha Trisha underscore GE e at on
Trisha Trisha在上强调了GE e
Twitter oh I meant to put that on the
Twitter哦，我打算将其放在
inside my forgot yeah and there were
我忘了里面，有
more questions coming out one more
还有更多问题
question is it possible to replace idea
问题有可能取代想法
build project with Gradle so that is
用Gradle建立专案
invoked on how
关于如何调用
keys as well as build project actions
键以及构建项目动作
triggered elsewhere hmm if I understood
如果我理解，在其他地方触发
correctly the question is whether it is
正确的问题是
possible to remember their shortcuts so
可能记得他们的捷径
instead of build project make project
代替构建项目
you could invoke compiled tasks in
您可以在以下位置调用已编译的任务
Gradle I believe it is possible so you
Gradle我相信有可能，所以你
you you you don't definitely can change
你你你肯定不会改变
change remove the shortcut from make the
更改从make删除快捷方式
project and assign a new one for any
项目并为任何项目分配一个新项目
task Gradle parts yeah I think that's it
Task Gradle部分是的，我认为就是这样
and if if you have more questions just
如果您还有其他问题，
yeah feel free to ask them in Twitter or
是的，请随时在Twitter上询问他们，或者
publish them as a comments to the
将它们发布为对
recording yeah absolutely I think that's
录音绝对是的，我认为那是
it so Thank You Trisha for presentation
所以谢谢Trisha的介绍
and I think thank everyone for your time
我想谢谢大家的时间
and for your questions take care and
对于您的问题请多加注意
have a good day
祝你有美好的一天